{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The typical parts list should include the ________.", "opta": "part number", "optb": "manufacturing material", "optc": "number of parts needed", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A typical set of mechanical working drawings includes ________.", "opta": "exploded assembly", "optb": "part details", "optc": "parts list", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The title block used on working drawings should include the ________.", "opta": "sheet number", "optb": "line type", "optc": "layer set", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One critical issue drafters need to pay close attention to is the ________.", "opta": "size of the sheet", "optb": "designer's intent", "optc": "scale factor", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In the mechanical design process the first step is to ________.", "opta": "brainstorm solutions", "optb": "prepare rough sketches", "optc": "prepare a budget", "optd": "identify the problem", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The text used on a typical detail sheet should be ________.", "opta": "placed horizontally", "optb": "in bold text", "optc": "in an architectural text style", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In an exploded assembly drawing it is customary for the drafter to use a ________ line to illustrate how parts fit together.", "opta": "Phantom", "optb": "hidden", "optc": "dashed", "optd": "center", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "It is customary for the first sheet of a working drawing set to include ________.", "opta": "a parts list", "optb": "exploded assembly", "optc": "assembled assembly", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In order to create an accurate assembly drawing the drafter should create the ________ drawings first.", "opta": "Detail", "optb": "title block", "optc": "parts list", "optd": "isometric", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The thread note for a typical bolt will include the ________.", "opta": "major diameter of the thread", "optb": "material", "optc": "center line", "optd": "offset distance", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}